Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/fibiee-liew (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Makeup Artistry
Creative Arts
Cosmetics

Languages

English (Professional Working)
Chinese (Professional Working)
Malay (Limited Working)
Cantonese (Limited Working)
Hakka (Native or Bilingual)

Fibiee Liew

Regional Trainer (Southeast Asia & India) at FOREO Kuala Lumpur

Summary

I am highly proficient in corporate beauty training, brand customer and retail experience, makeup artistry, skin knowledge and basic medical aesthetic knowledge. I have vast experiences of 11 years in professional beauty experiences in this specific field.

Experience

FOREO

Regional Trainer (Southeast Asia & India) March 2019 - September 2020 (1 year 7 months)

Benefit Cosmetics
Brand Trainer
January 2018 - February 2019 (1 year 2 months)

KOSÉ Corporation

Beauty Trainer

June 2016 - August 2017 (1 year 3 months)

- Conduct training for product knowledge, technique and also selling skills to all the beauty advisors
- Conduct and facilitate in workshop and also consumer events
- Design an instructional design to conduct the training based on local market
- Conduct coaching on field such as counter coaching on product knowledge and also make sure beauty advisor is implementing what have taught in classroom
- Evaluate beauty advisor's performance and career development
- Conduct NEW beauty advisor training to equip beauty advisor with all the product knowledge and selling skills
- Assist training manager in preparing the training text and also materials
- Support roadshow events and also other related activities
- Magazine photoshoot makeup support and also other related shoots

The Estée Lauder Companies Inc.

Beauty Consultant

January 2015 - December 2016 (2 years)

- Provide customer service to clients and customers by providing skin care and makeup advice, and also retaining repeat clientele
- Achieve counter target sales by measuring the sales in units and total sales
- Keeping up with all the latest product knowledge and skin care knowledge to provide advice to customers
- Selling techniques in skin care and makeup products to achieve counter's sales
- Recommend the ideal products for customers based on their preference and also products which is suitable for the customers
- Provide skin care service and also makeup service for customers
- Assist counter manager in stock take
- Take responsibility of counter cleanliness
- Replenish stock and also assist in product stock arrangement in counter

CHANEL

Beauty Advisor

October 2014 - December 2016 (2 years 3 months)

- Provide customer service to clients and customers by providing skin care and makeup advice, and also retaining repeat clientele
- Achieve counter target sales by measuring the sales in units and total sales
- Keeping up with all the latest product knowledge and skin care knowledge to provide advice to customers
- Selling techniques in skin care and makeup products to achieve counter's sales
- Recommend the ideal products for customers based on their preference and also products which is suitable for the customers
- Provide skin care service and also makeup service for customers
- Assist counter manager in stock take
- Take responsibility of counter cleanliness
- Replenish stock and also assist in product stock arrangement in counter

FL.Makeup

Founding Artist & Lead Face Artist/Trainer 2010 - 2016 (6 years)

- A makeup beauty platform that founded by Fibiee Liew herself with a group of 10 makeup artist working based on projects to provide customise designed makeup services for all the clientele

- Conduct training to educate aspiring makeup artist by educating them with makeup knowledge, techniques and skills.
- Exposed to weddings, stage productions, fashion show, print ads, commercial shooting, beauty pageants, wedding, events, photo shoots and etc.
- Work was also appeared in various online and offline platform such as social media platform, prints ads, magazines cover and etc.
- Worked with local personalities and international personalities, celebrities and beauty queen
- Collaboration with established brands and involvement of sponsorships
- Attended media launches and social events as a makeup expert
- Delivered and creating content such as beauty knowledge, product reviews and lifestyle tips
- Educating beauty and makeup knowledge, personal grooming and overall image styling to all her clients
- High ability to design a makeup to suits the client's features and able to identify the needs of the client
- Clientete base include stablished brands like Maybank, Popular, Hotlink, MaGIC
- Lead a group 10 highly skilled makeup artist to run and coordinate a fashion show "Face of Malaysia 2016"

Education

University of Hertfordshire, United Kingdom
Bachelor's Degree, Double Major Degree in Marketing & Event Management
(School of Business) · (2014 - 2016)

INTI International University & Colleges
Diploma, Business Administration · (2010 - 2013)

Inspiration by William Yap
Advanced Makeup & Hair Bridal Image Styling · (2016 - 2016)

MALSWISSE SCHOOL OF BEAUTY AND WELLNESS Advanced Professional Makeup Course · (2012 - 2012)

Cosmoprof Academy (Singapore)
Advanced Make-up Techniques · (2018 - 2018)